livemusicguide.com 2013-05-03

# Privacy Policy : Live Music Guide

The Townshend Group, LLC (the "Company") respects your privacy and the security of your personal data. This Privacy Policy explains how we treat and safeguard personal information. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully prior to your access to and/or use of **www.LiveMusicGuide.com** (the "Website"). If you do not agree with the terms of the Privacy Policy, please do not use our Website.

By using this Website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use. This Privacy Policy is subject to the Terms of Use, which includes all disclaimers of warranties and limitation of liabilities. All capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meaning set forth in the Terms of Use.

_**Collected Information**_

The Company does not collect personally identifying information about any individual Website user except when knowingly provided by such individual. For example, we may ask you for information, such as your name, email address, or other personal details when you register to become a member of the Website. You may also provide information to the Website in order to enter into a sweepstakes or promotion. We also at time might supplement the data you provide to us with data from data append services. You always have the option not to provide the information we request. If you choose not to provide such information, you can still visit the Website, but you may be unable to access certain parts of the Website.

_**Data Analytics**_

"Cookies" are alphanumeric identifiers in the form of text files that are inserted and stored by your web browser on your computer's hard drive. The Company uses cookies to track web and advertising analytics throughout the Website and to store preferential information about you. The data read from these cookies may be linked to personally identifying and non-personally identifying information.

You may reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to allow your browser to alert you when a cookie is set. However, if you select these settings you may be unable to access certain parts of the Website.

Web beacons, also known as pixel tags and clear GIFs, are electronic images that allow a website to access cookies and help track marketing campaigns and general usage patterns of visitors to those websites. Web beacons can recognize certain types of information, such as cookie numbers, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page where the web beacons are placed. We may use web beacons in order to recognize users, assess traffic patterns, identify preferred content and measure site interaction. 

We may also use a reputable third party to collect information, including through the use of web beacons, browser cookies and other tracking technologies. We may collect via web beacons various data provided by your browser while you are on our site and elsewhere where we may be acting as a third party. This data is collected in the aggregate but may include or be associated with other non-personally identifiable information (PII) or PII that users have voluntarily submitted.

The Website and ad servers log information about a site user's IP address, browser type and the current URL the user is requesting. This information is always provided by each and every user's browser. These log files are stored in a secure location and used—in an aggregated, anonymous manner—in our internal analysis of traffic patterns within our Website. This information is automatically logged by most websites.

_**Use of Information**_

We collect user information to enhance your experience on our Website. We use aggregated (gathered up data across all user accounts) information to develop content targeted to users' interests and to better the Website user experience.

We use data analytics collected by the systems described above to develop and provide content and advertising that is targeted to your interests. Such technology is used to determine which areas of our Website you prefer based upon the frequency of your visits and engagement with those areas. We may make assumptions based on your browser provided data to target relevant content and advertising to you. We may also make geographic and demographic assumptions based on your presented IP address to target relevant content and advertising.

To enhance your experience, we may provide you with interactive communications or emails to the email address that you provide to us. Such communications are provided only to users who have expressly provided us with their permission to receive them as part of their user profile.

We respect the privacy of our users and will not disclose or distribute our user list to any third party, nor permit anyone else to do so, without a user's express permission. We may make available for rental our list of those users who have expressly provided us with their permission to receive third party offers as part of their user profile. In those cases, your email address will be transferred to the third party for one time use.

Registered users may change the information stored in their member profile and may elect to stop receiving marketing material from the Company or on behalf of external third party business partners. You may also request to delete your personal account if you wish to do so. Please email us at the contact information included below.

_**Sharing of Information**_

When you are on an area of LiveMusicGuide.com and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with LiveMusicGuide.com, as well as its business partners and vendors.

We use third parties to provide credit card processing, email service providers and hosting services on our site. When you sign up for such services, we will share your personally identifiable information as necessary for the third party to provide that service. These third parties are prohibited from using your PII for any other purpose. If you do not want your information to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer of your information by not using that particular service. In addition, if you provide any PII via an advertiser promotion, please be aware you are directly providing your PII to that advertiser.

From time to time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain PII from you, such as your name and email. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary, and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. We may use this PII to notify contest winners and award prizes.

We may also use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests; that company will be prohibited from using our users' PII for any other purpose. We will not share the PII you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and an opportunity to opt out.

We may also have features that allow you to send an email to yourself and/or others about an item on our site. If you choose to use our email referral service, you will be required to provide the email address or addresses that will be used in the notification. Upon form submission, an email will be generated to your recipient(s) inviting them to visit the URL you have recommended. We may not store this information other than for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email.

_**Information Provided to Advertisers**_

The Company derives the majority of its revenue from advertising and sharing information is essential to keeping our services affordable to users. In order to attract and retain advertisers, we use the aggregated, anonymous information that we gather (as well as information from third-party market researchers) to describe our services to partners and to assist our advertisers and sponsors to better understand our audience. We only share PII with advertisers when users have expressly provided us with their permission to receive third party offers as part of their user profile.

_**As Necessary to Provide Services to You**_

We may occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of newsletter mailings, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our services. We will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service. In some instances these companies may collect information directly from you. In these cases, you will be notified of the involvement of the external service provider. In all cases, these companies are subject to agreements that require them to maintain the confidentiality of your information, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

_**Security**_

The Company uses commercially accepted security measures to protect any personal information provided by you to this Website. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your submitted information, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to our Website, and you do so at your own risk. We will not be responsible for any damages directly or indirectly caused by an unauthorized third party's ability to view, use or disseminate personal information.

The Company urges you to keep your password in a safe place and not to divulge it to anyone. Remember to log off your account and close your browser window when you have finished your visit to our Website. This is to ensure that others cannot access your account, especially if you are sharing a computer with someone else.

_**Link to Third Party Websites**_

The Website is linked to third party websites which are not maintained by the Company. Such third party websites are not under the Company's control, and the Company is not responsible or liable for and does not warrant the contents of, technology implemented by, or privacy practices of any such linked website. You should review the privacy policy and terms of use for each of these websites to make sure they are acceptable to you prior to your use.

_**Enforcement of Law**_

We will disclose PII upon receipt of a court order or subpoena or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation. We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we, in good faith, believe to be unlawful.

_**In the Event of Merger, Sale or Bankruptcy**_

In the event that the Company is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used.

_**Changes to this Privacy Policy**_

The Company reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to update, amend and/or change this Privacy Policy without prior notice and at any time. Updates to this Privacy Policy will be posted here. You are encouraged to visit this Privacy Policy from time to time in order to review any changes that have been made. Your continued use of the Website following the posting of any such changes will automatically be deemed to constitute your acceptance of all changes. The Company's last update to this Privacy Policy was made and posted on 05-02-2013.

_**Questions or Concerns**_

If you have questions, comments, concerns or feedback regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us via any of the methods set forth below: .
